{
    "subject": "resource/Spectrasonics",
    "predicate": "ontology/keyPerson",
    "object": "resource/Eric_Persing",
    "human_readable": "Eric Persing is a key person associated with Spectrasonics.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9221435785293579,
            "question": "Are there any other key figures associated with Spectrasonics besides Eric Persing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9183239936828613,
            "question": "What role does Eric Persing play at Spectrasonics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8994998931884766,
            "question": "Who is Eric Persing associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8938519358634949,
            "question": "What impact has Eric Persing had on Spectrasonics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8511988520622253,
            "question": "What is the overall significance of Eric Persing's work in the context of Spectrasonics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5515877604484558,
            "question": "Can you name any products associated with Spectrasonics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5125143527984619,
            "question": "What are some notable achievements of Eric Persing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4300041198730469,
            "question": "What is Spectrasonics known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40627583861351013,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Eric Persing and the music industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33430108428001404,
            "question": "Has Eric Persing received any awards or recognition for his work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Eric Persing is a key person associated with Spectrasonics.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5914_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a connection between Eric Persing and the music industry?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5914_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Spectrasonics known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5914_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some notable achievements of Eric Persing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5914_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5914_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5914_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5914_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5914_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5914_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5914_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5914_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5914_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5914_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5914_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here's my evaluation:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention Eric Persing as the founder and creative director of Spectrasonics (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5914/re-ranker-msmarco/8.txt), and later confirm that he is indeed the founder of Spectrasonics (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5914/re-ranker-msmarco/61.txt, file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5914/re-ranker-msmarco/63.txt). This information supports the triple that Eric Persing is a key person associated with Spectrasonics."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide multiple references to Eric Persing as the founder and head of Spectrasonics, indicating his significant role in the company."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}